{
    "subject": "resource/Amy_Winehouse",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Grammy_Award_winners",
    "human_readable": "Amy Winehouse is a Grammy Award winner.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9697626829147339,
            "question": "What category did Amy Winehouse win the Grammy Award in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9622350335121155,
            "question": "What year did Amy Winehouse win the Grammy Award?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9121363759040833,
            "question": "What award did Amy Winehouse win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6915659308433533,
            "question": "Who is Amy Winehouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5557079911231995,
            "question": "What is Amy Winehouse's legacy in music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5232557058334351,
            "question": "What genre of music was Amy Winehouse known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39143359661102295,
            "question": "Where was Amy Winehouse from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3837979733943939,
            "question": "What are some of Amy Winehouse's most popular songs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28744935989379883,
            "question": "Is Amy Winehouse still alive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2760467231273651,
            "question": "When was Amy Winehouse born?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Amy Winehouse is a Grammy Award winner.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5765_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Amy Winehouse still alive?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5765_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Amy Winehouse's most popular songs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5765_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Amy Winehouse from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5765_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5765_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5765_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5765_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5765_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5765_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5765_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5765_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5765_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5765_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5765_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Amy Winehouse winning Grammy Awards, supporting the statement that she is a Grammy Award winner."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}